Brian Alexander

Internship - New Jersey - Geneses Bio-Tech

Mercerville, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Brian-Alexander/8ec842a0c041f89f

Highly motivated, detail-oriented with the ability to troubleshoot and quickly resolve problems, and find effective solutions. Experienced in manufacturing production, assembly, quality assurance machine operation, and maintenance, installations and repairs of complicated equipment to specifications

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship - New Jersey

Geneses Bio-Tech - 2014 to Present

Stationary Engineer (NJ Black Seal)

- Systems Operations / High Pressure Boilers
- Maintained Systems
- · Chemical Water Analysis

Lead Pressman

AFL Web Printing - Voorhees, NJ - 2007 to 2013

Responsible for various printing processes such as design, color printing and manual procedures

- Maintained schedule of routine maintenance for presses
- Produced reports of tracking productivity of presses
- Customer Service
- Implemented new procedures for cost effectiveness and quality control
- Made sure that products were produced on a timely bases with quality control
- Responsible for the selection and maintenance of equipment

Forman/ Pressman

Trenton Times - Trenton, NJ - 1987 to 2006

Responsible for the selection and maintenance of equipment

- Employed root cause analysis to troubleshoot equipment and process issues
- Multi-tasked to keep all assigned projects running effectively and efficiently
- Managed the daily schedule and productivity of six employees
- Negotiated and worked with editors on all facets or the printing including design, color printing and manual processes business
- Contributed to overall productivity in facility

EDUCATION

Vocational in Engineering Black Seal

Mercer County Community College - Trenton, NJ 2007

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS

Process Engineering

- Equipment problem resolution
- Shop Math